Qashif U Rehman

Summary

Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous skills including HTML5, CSS3, ReatJs, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Git. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- React
- HTML5
- Tailwind CSS

Redux

DOB: 19-11-1989

Mohali Chandigarh

- CSS
- Laravel
- Axios

Experience

Web Developer - 07/2022 to 10/2023

KashoSoft Labs, Baramulla

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Technical Associate: 01/2016 to 06/2022 **Compsoft Solutions**, Model Town, Sopore

Business Development Associate: 03/2012 to 10/2015

Comsoft Solutions: Model Town, Sopore

Education

Bachelor in Computer Applications: 2007-2010

University Of Kashmir